

HASSAN AL-HASHIMI

UX/UI DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Passionate and talented UX Designer with experience of Frontend Development, designing with HTML, CSS and Javascript in Atom. Have completed a couple projects using Figma and Wix as my primary tools and expanding my skills by designing with other editors such as Webflow, Sketch and Adobe XD.

CONTACT

- +1-672-999-9093
- Hassan_Al-Hashimi@hotmail.com
- https://hassanal-hashimi.wixsite.com/uxportfolio
- Vancouver, Canada
- github.com/suushiixcoding

RELEVANT SKILLS



TOOLS

Figma	80%	Marvel	90%
Jira	70%	Adobe Photoshop	60%
Adobe XD	80%	Adobe InDesign	80%
Sketch	60%	Atom	50%

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

UX DESIGNER

Volunteer - Monaa Project

09/2022 - Present

- Collaborating with another UX Designer to deliver full featured app of womens health
- · Creating user flows based on proto persona
- Responsible for competitor research, conceptual visual wireframing
- Low High Fidelity wireframing and reiterations of design
- Prototyping of product and progressing with A/B and preference testing of finished features in app

WEB DESIGNER

Freelance - FPC Project

06/2022 - 09/2022

- Completed a full website redesign based on client's previous website concept
- Achieving completion of website within timeframe while being informed to switch from Wix to Webflow website editor.
- Reiterating the website based on the clients chosen ideas through UI concepts and development

RELATED EXPERIENCE

ARCHITECTURAL ASSISTANT

K&J Consulting Engineers

2019 - 2019

- Prepare the drawings and the planning of Leicester Meridian Leisure Park (Vue Cinema). The proposal works involves Unit – B for Prezzo, alterations to the front entrance, provision of additional doors and service penetrations within elevations and roof.
- Prepare the drawings and the planning of Image
 House, Coombe Avenue, Croydon CRO. Two storey
 including four flats following the demolition of the
 existing traditional cut timber pitched, steel frame,
 beam and block ground floor and PC first floor.

ARCHITECTURAL DESIGNER

Freelance

2018 - 2018

- Preparing 2D drawings using AutoCAD and the planning and organisation of each floor, sections and elevations
- Creating a 3D model of the drawings using Revit and applying the structural elements to express the strategy used for the buildings
- Renders of model and post production in Lumion and Photoshop
- Technical drawings made in AutoCAD measuring floor plans and site boundaries

ARCHITECTURAL ASSISTANT

Murphy Philipps Architects

2016 - 2016

- Understanding the architecture plan of work
- · Experienced site visit with architects for planning
- Working on a small scale project to design a pavilion for a regeneration of a social community
- · Learning time frame and budget
- Working on several programs such as Microstation, Sketchup, Photoshop and InDesign

EDUCATION

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT

CareerFoundry

10/2022 - 11/2022

UX DESIGN

CareerFoundry

09/2021 - 09/2022

(BA) ARCHITECTURE DEGREE

Birmingham City University

09/2013 - 06/2017

BTEC EXTENDED DIPLOMA - ART & DESIGN

City of Westminster College

09/2011 - 07/2013

ACHIEVEMENTS

AWARD FOR BCU COLLABORATIVE PROJECT FOR THE HS2

Birmingham City University

09/2015 - 11/2015

Worked on a collaboration project with University of Birmingham to design a temporary viewing gallery for the proposed Curzon Street Station for HS2.

INTERESTS

